<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.libtv" version="0.11.2" name="LibTV" provider-name="You">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="context.py"/>
    <extension point="kodi.context.item">
        <menu id="kodi.core.main">
            <item library="context.py">
                <label>32113</label>
                <visible>Player.HasVideo</visible>
            </item>
        </menu>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">LibTV - Your Kodi Library as Real TV</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Turn your movies and TV shows into linear channels with full TV guide support. Generates an M3U playlist and XMLTV guide for PVR IPTV Simple Client, with plugin-resolved streams so channels play whatever is currently on air.</description>
        <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <news>v0.11.2: fix the EPG overlay opening on the wrong channel and changing the live channel while browsing. The overlay now opens with its cursor already on the currently-playing channel (a new libtv_channel_id ListItem property, same mechanism as the join-in-progress seek offset); navigation moved from Up/Down to Left/Right since Up/Down was confirmed to actually change the live channel via Kodi's native channel-surf, not just show a preview.

v0.11.1: fix IPTV Simple auto-configuration giving no visible feedback at all when IPTV Simple was disabled (found testing live). Now shows a "Configuring..." notification immediately, and uses a blocking dialog instead of a toast for the two failures that need action from you (not installed/enabled, or something playing) so they can't go unnoticed.

v0.11.0: refine IPTV Simple auto-configuration - M3U/EPG paths are now written as special:// URLs instead of resolved OS paths (confirmed pvr.iptvsimple reads local files through Kodi's VFS either way), the instance is now named after a new "Instance name" setting instead of a fixed "LibTV" string, and an existing same-named instance is now looked up by its actual content (not just a fixed id) and never silently overwritten - if one already exists with different settings, LibTV asks before changing it.</news>
    </extension>
</addon>
