<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.libtv" version="0.7.9" name="LibTV" provider-name="You">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="context.py"/>
    <extension point="kodi.context.item">
        <menu id="kodi.core.main">
            <item library="context.py">
                <label>32113</label>
                <visible>Player.HasVideo</visible>
            </item>
        </menu>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">LibTV - Your Kodi Library as Real TV</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Turn your movies and TV shows into linear channels with full TV guide support. Generates an M3U playlist and XMLTV guide for PVR IPTV Simple Client, with plugin-resolved streams so channels play whatever is currently on air.</description>
        <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <news>v0.7.9: replace the EPG overlay's ControlList (which rendered nothing at all, even after four fix attempts) with plain ControlLabels and hand-rolled up/down navigation and row highlighting, since a no-skin ControlList's item-rendering path was clearly the problem, not any one parameter.

v0.7.8: fix the EPG overlay showing a background but no text at all — the ControlList had no explicit font (nothing to fall back to without a skin) and used label/label2, which a bare no-skin list has no defined layout for. Now sets an explicit font and combines Now/Next into a single label per row.

v0.7.7: fix the EPG overlay being completely invisible — a code-only WindowDialog draws no background of its own, and the ControlList had no explicit text colors, so it opened and closed correctly (confirmed via log + double-Esc test) but rendered nothing on screen. Added a small bundled background image behind the list plus explicit text/selected colors so rows are legible over playing video.</news>
    </extension>
</addon>
